yoursite.com 2004-04-05

# BlockAllSpam - The End Of Spam - Guaranteed

Privacy and safety issues are important to us; what follows are the details that describe our privacy policy.

Regarding the utilization of User's ( customer or blockallspam.com visitor ) data, Block All Spam does not sell or otherwise share specific user information with any unrelated third party. No User data is acquired for any unsolicited contact. Block All Spam has, and enforces, an anti-spam policy.

Block All Spam may disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with ( either intentionally or unintentionally ) Block All Spam's rights or property, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Block All Spam may disclose user information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.

Block All Spam may share aggregate information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors and other third parties. For example, we will say Block All Spam's audience is x percent females and y percent males. Individual or company information is not shared. 

|  There are cases where Block All Spam may ask you for personal information such as your name or email address. For example, we request personal information when you subscribe to Block All Spam's services. Block All Spam needs to collect this information for the normal operation of our mutual business purpose as well as federal, state and local laws.

The importance of security for all personally identifiable information associated with our users is of utmost concern to us. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Block All Spam can't ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. When credit card information is transmitted we use industry standard, SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption.   
  
---|---
